"Inspector Chan"
"Super Crime Fighters"
Who else?
You arrested
a beautiful woman like her
just for spitting?
Is there no justice?
Is there no law?
Your boss wouldn't
bemake Commissioner,
if he hadn't paid respect
to the Crocodile Gang.
And you don't freaking know me?
Sorry, I didn't know
she's your wife.
Ugly coward, stop dodging!
Let's go!
What are you looking at?
Never seen such
a handsome gang boss before?
Any business but the film business!
There is not a single person
in the theater on Sunday.
Where's the car?
Let's go back in!
Call for help!
No need for that, Northerner.
While you were messing
with hitting the cop,
your men signed up with us.
I'll kill all you Axe Gang!
Hold on it!
You forgotten that time
I had treated you to dinner.
Brother Sum.
Please...
Please spare me.
Don't worry.
I don't kill women. You can go!
Thank you, Big Brother.
The cops!
Come out and clean up the mess!
"The Axe Gang"
"Cage Walled City"
- Why butting?
- I'm in a hurry.
Get to the end of the line!
(One, two, three!)
That OK, Coollie?
No problem!
"Tailor Shop"
"Noodles and Congee"
Check please, Donut.
How much?
It's on the house!
I like you!
- Donut.
- It's nothing...
I go back.
I'll talk to the wife
about lowering your rent.
Thank you!
Mornin' landlord!
Landlord!
Jill, how you haved grown!
Come over and let me examine you!
Landlord, good to see you!
What so good about it?
Don't...
Mr. Tailor,
can you raise the skirt's slit?
Sure!
Look, comet!
Jane, you naughty girl!
Hey, Landlord! You're such a scamp!
Don't go, Jane!
Come have a chat!
Don't take it seriously.
Jane!
Landlady!
What happened? There's no water?
Water ain't free!
You're talking too much
for someone who won't pay his rent.
But I'm in the middle of a shampoo.
You shouldn't close the tap!
That's only the start
of your problems.
From now on, no water on Mondays,
Wednesdays and Fridays!
Water ration on Tuesdays,
Thursdays and Saturdays!
I just love hearing
you fools complain!
Arse-holes!
Good Morning, Landlady!
What so good about it?
Just pay your rent!
I will burn your store.
What so funny?
So funny
and you don't have to pay rent?
Serves you right to be a coolie!
Months late on your rent
and you won't even
say "Good Morning".
You'll be a coolie for life.
There you go, handsome!
You! What took you so long
with the congee?
I am back.
I stopped to help an old lady
cross the street.
Then what're you doing here?
Checking if there're peeping toms.
Auntie Six, did someone just spy
on you peep when you bathed?
Don't shoot your mouth off
without proof.
She's crazy.
Go away!
Sir Uncle, can you please teach us?
No more soccer!
Who wants the cut?
My boss.
Have a seat.
Done! 50 cents please.
Isn't it great?
It's too good!
Why make him look so good?
Why?
Don't get mad, Boss.
This is my longtime buddy.
I'll handle this.
He's the Boss of the Axe Gang.
Don't you see those two axes?
We are bad guys.
Making him look so good
is really bad!
- Don't you know?
- I did not know.
You're a numb skull!
But I like you,
so why don't you just pay me,
and I'll take care of it.
No way!
Don't use that axes just yet, Boss.
Let me talk to him.
I really care for you.
You saw it with your own eyes.
I ain't lying.
Why don't you pay up?
Just a little. For make-up drinks.
So you're blackmailing me!
Boss!
Boss...
You're dead now!
Looks like he's waking up soon!
I'm not afraid. You can kill me,
but there'll be
thousands more of me!
You wanna play rough?
This is the Axe Gang Boss,
taking a nap inside.
Whoever wants to die?
Please step forward.
So you wanna rough house play?
Great! We'll go one-on-one.
Don't even think about cheating!
The old woman with the onion.
You look so tough.
You wanna try me?
I'll let you hit me first!
What do you do?
I'm a farmer.
You're a farmer.
You shouldn't fight.
Why don't you scram!
He's crazy!
Calling me names?
You're lucky that you're a woman!
You, shortie!
Yeah, you!
If you're short,
you must not retort!
Hey, I don't like cheaters.
Sit back down!
You, the uncle with glasses,
you look so mean.
No, not you, I mean...
You!
Hey kid, let's rumble!
Alright!
So we won't have
any one-on-ones today.
You people are such wimps!
He blackmailed me.
Fat woman,
you're in charge here, right?
Fat woman my arse!
I'm with the Axe Gang!
Axe Gang my arse!
- Boss!
- Boss my arse!
You have to pay for
our medical bills!
- Medical bills my arse!
- Hey, we're on the same side!
Same side my arse!
Stop!
Think you're so tough?
I'll call back up!
You nitwit!
Let's see how you call back up!
You don't know
what kinda backing I have.
Don't you go away!
Go ahead and put a down payment
on your coffin!
Who threw the firecracker?
I'm one of you, Brother.
Don't be nosy!
It's raining.
Go, bring your laundry!
Fat woman!
You're blackmailing me too?
I ain't afraid.
I...
Did anyone see what happened?
Don't!
My back is broken!
Call for help!
Move!
Hold on, don't get mad.
You hungry? I have...
Shut up!
Don't move,
or I'll chop you to death!
Who's responsible?
I'll count to three.
One...
Two...
I did it!
Help!
Brother Sum, are the goods OK?
Sorry!
Don't look, kid. Turn away.
Take that away!
We're the bad guys!
Not the other way round!
We got our arses kicked today.
All because these two morons
called themselves Axes!
Don't bother with this,
Brother Sum.
You're in no shape mood for this!
You, take care of it!
Hey, he can really pick locks.
Just making a living.
Give me a chance.
If you're so good,
why don't you pick that one too!
Get ready.
I'll count to three.
Hurry!
Ready? Three...
He is quick!
Brother Sum,
I really want to be an Axe.
That's why I did what I did.
Give me a chance.
You killed anyone before?
I've always thought about
killing people.
Then kill someone!
I will!
Go on!
Thank you, Brother Sum!
We can always find
a use for his kind.
I told you before,
you must look tough!
Tougher!
How could you fall asleep?
Unprofessional!
It's tiring to be tough.
Tiring? We're making a living!
In this world, the streets
are filled with money and women.
Whoever has the will
and determination will triumph.
Whoever makes use of opportunity
can be a winner.
Now we have a chance!
We just kill someone,
and we're in the gang!
Then it'll be money
and women all the way!
Don't be like those beggars,
no ambitions!
Hey, what you looking at,
Four-Eyes?
I'll smash your glasses!
Get lost!
Get down here and say that!
You really going to kill someone?
Of course!
I'll kill all the Four-Eyes,
and the fat woman,
and all the people in Pig's Cage!
But they're good at kung fu.
Kung fu? I'm good too!
Oh yeah?
Think I'd tell you
if I knew Buddhist Palm kung fu?
Hey there, handsome boy. Stop!
Amazing!
Did you know
you have a special aura?
You are so young
but with the bone structure
and "chi" flow of a kung fu genius.
If one day,
your chi flow is channeled,
you will be invincible!
"You cannot escape your destiny."
The duty of upholding world peace,
and punishing evil will go to you.
This is the scroll of
the Buddhist Palm. It's priceless.
But I'll let you have it for $10.
Just because it's fate!
"The Buddhist Palm"
You gave him your life savings?
I was saving to study
to be a doctor or lawyer,
but it was world peace...
"First, The Buddha's Aura Appeared"
"Second, Nanga Asked the Buddha"
Let go of the girl!
Why it's the Buddhist Palm!
The "20 Cent Kung Fu Manual".
Have you killed anyone lately?
You are loaded!
One's a fool, the other's mute.
Go kill yourselves! Losers!
Since then, I realized that
good guys finish last.
I want to be bad.
To kill, and not be killed!
- Ice cream!
- Where?
Two... Vanilla for me!
Chocolate here!
What you looking at?
Never seen free ice cream before?
Look at her run!
You're such kung fu masters.
Go sell it as an act!
You're better off
in the circus than here!
Don't say that, Landlady.
They have their reasons.
Everyone has his reasons.
We don't want to make trouble.
I'm glad you get it.
We won't hear the end of it
with the mob mad at us.
Why don't you get lost!
Your wife shouldn't be so mean.
You OK?
Masters...
We have nothing precious
to give you,
but take this as a token of
our appreciation.
Thanks for saving us!
Save your crying.
This is not a show!
You are cold hearted.
Talking back to me?
You may know kung fu
but you're still a sissy.
It's no crime
being good at kung fu!
Once a sissy, always a sissy.
Look at you.
Why do you wear red underwear?
Why not a diaper
while you're at it?
What's wrong with red underwear?
Where were you
when there was trouble?
If not for them,
it could've been the end for us.
Be reasonable!
I'll reason with you
You owe me three months rent.
That'll be $90.
Pay up or pack up!
Don't you worry. I'll pay for them.
Trying to be a smartarse,
Bucktooth Jane?
That's right. What're you
going to do about it, Tub of Lard?
Witch!
They owe me rent.
Dare you!
You trying to drown me out?
The fat lady can really sing.
Watch me give it to her!
What happened?
What do you mean what happened?
You try it!
Me?
Hurry!
Sorry, you OK?
I think you should move forward
and take better aim.
OK?
OK!
Who's throwing the handles?
The handles?
Where's the third knife's handles?
God knows where you threw it.
Could this be the same one?
It can't be...
- Don't!
- Sorry.
You trying to say something?
I just remembered
I have something to do.
See you!
Oh no! They've seen us!
Don't come near!
"Snake gallbladder"
Don't panic! Snakes like music.
Once I blow my whistle,
they won't bite!
Please don't blow it again.
I'll blow...
It's you again, arsehole!
Go back to your business!
Nothing to see here!
Let's split up!
Split?
What're you doing here?
Waiting for you! Weren't you hurt?
I'm fine!
How come you always recover
so fast?
I don't know.
Which hospital did you go to?
Don't remember!
Maybe it's better this way.
"Memories can be painful,
forgetting maybe a blessing!"
Never knew you were so deep.
"All the sadness one can bear,
down the river everywhere."
Hey, get out of the way!
Move!
I'll slap you to kingdom come!
Look at those Four Eyes,
walking around with a coffin!
What morons!
Don't blame me
for forcing you out.
We'll let Buddha decide
whether you stay or leave.
"Horrifically Bad Fate"
Have some tea.
We're grateful
that professionals like you
can help.
We understand.
12 Kicks of the Tam School,
Iron Fist of the Hung School,
and the Hexagon Staff.
Those guys at Pig's Cage are good.
They were all top fighters,
who retired from their Warrior Days.
This job,
is a great challenge for us.
This is what I call professionalism.
Number One Killers.
Maybe expensive,
but worth every penny!
No! Number One is the Beast,
the world's top killer.
He was so dedicated to kung fu
that he went crazy.
I heard he's now in an asylum.
So you are the top killers now.
Technically speaking,
we're musicians.
"A song that wrenches the heart,
where do I find a knowing ear?"
Wonderful poem, isn't it?
We'll be saying goodbye soon.
Don't know
when we'll see each other again.
So we're three one of a kind.
Wish I'd known before.
Let's take advantage
of the situation
and spar a little.
Nah, we still have a lot to pack.
- Yes, you're right.
- Yes.
12 Kicks of the Tam School,
superb attack and defense!
Iron Fist, powerful yet delicate,
Top-notch!
Hexagon Staff,
with its thousand moves. Mystical!
See you again...
More lipstick!
When stir-frying,
the heat must be high.
That's right.
Keep stir-frying.
Stop! I'll kill you!
Sorry, we're not open for business.
You can make me
something in no time!
We're moving!
This is good material!
You know your stuff.
This has high artistic value!
How high?
A few stories high!
They're asking for it,
picking on the Axe Gang.
We'll take them out
and make this place a brothel.
Don't block my view!
What's going on?
Good...
Don't block my view!
Darn! I told those nitwits to leave,
but they're still here
and now the gangs are back!
- Really?
- Yeah!
What? Having a fight here?
Who'll pay for the damages?
Sorry. It's nothing!
Stop the noise.
You know what time it is?
I have to sleep!
Hey Fatso, go to sleep!
But this is a lot of noise!
Sorry!
Stay out of my way!
You okay?
Stop the noise!
Give us a break!
Why push us so far?
Still have proficient.
It really is the Lion's Roar!
I thought it was a myth!
The Lion's Roar!
Tai Chi!
That's the last.
We'll see of them.
It's bad, Brother Sum.
Start the car, quick!
Start the car!
Boss!
Keep it down! Have you no manners?
Who the heck are you?
People here have to sleep!
They have to work tomorrow.
Get out of here!
Scumbags!
I won't last long.
But to be able to see real masters,
I can now die in peace!
Don't say that.
We're ordinary folks.
It's a blessing to be ordinary.
We don't want
to be called masters.
You're such greatgood fighters!
If only you'd helped earlier,
they wouldn't have to die this way.
Like Donut said,
everyone has his reasons.
Years ago,
we saw our own son
killed in a fight.
Revenge can be devastating.
Hope you all understand.
Why don't you train us
to be top fighters,
and we'll avenge them!
Becoming a top fighter takes time.
Unless you're a natural.
You don't find one in a million.
It's obvious that I'm that very one.
Doesn't look like it.
Everyone, we swore that
we'd never fight again.
But we broke our promise today.
For your safety,
everyone should leave!
The more powerful,
the greater the responsibility.
You can't hide from it.
Donut, you're badly hurt.
Rest yourself.
Why don't you speak Chinese?
Donut!
Donut...
I know you, Four Eyes!
You seem to be biased
against the near-sighted.
That's right.
Especially those with gold frames.
Gold frame glasses
are perfect for clerks.
I think they look good on me.
It fits me.
But why do you keep picking on me?
Help out!
Help out! Help out!
Want to play punks?
The Dragon Style? The Tiger Style?
Get down here
and I'll smash your glasses
Come on!
You don't believe me?
You swear to it!
Swear!
You giving me no respect?
I asked you to help out,
but what were you doing?
What're you, a puppy? Woof!
You should at least play a bulldog.
We always get beat everytime!
All this time,
we haven't gotten anywhere.
No killing, no arson,
no robberies, no rapes,
all because of you!
You're a numb nut!
Follow me!
It's a stick up! Where's the money?
Where's the money?
What're you looking at?
Don't believe me? I'm serious!
Where is it? I kill people for less,
give me the money.
The money's here!
"Do you remember?"
"You saved me before."
Let go of the girl!
One's a fool, the other's mute.
Go kill yourselves! Losers!
"Thank you."
Stop following me!
You'll drag me down sooner or later.
Go home
and raise pigs!
Go, before I'll kill you!
Hey, what's your name?
Take this and get some new clothes.
You're now an Axe!
For real?
A friend is waiting for you.
Brother Sum!
I took one look at you,
and I knew you'd
do anything!
Right!
And you were just waiting
for your chance.
Right!
We need you for one thing!
Anything, Brother Sum!
"Atypical Pathology Center"
Hurry up!
"Research on Abnormal People."
What's that?
Mental asylum!
Good morning, Sir!
Soldiers!
Boy Scouts!
Tanks!
Don't worry about it.
When the Boy Scouts change shifts,
you have exactly 5 minutes
to get to the basement.
Follow the map.
Go to the last cell,
and get take the man out.
It's that simple!
Here's your tools.
What about you guys?
We'll be your lookouts!
Only 5 minutes. Hurry!
The World's Top Killer
indeed looks the part!
It's only a title!
Let's cut the nonsense.
We want you to kill two people.
Name your price!
Name my what?
I've killed many,
trying to find a worthy adversary
who can kill me.
So far,
I've never found one.
That is why I stayed inside.
I would have been out long ago.
Honestly, if you find
a worthy opponent,
I won't charge you a thing.
I'll do it for free.
Have you found someone?
Yes, brilliant fighters,
who are up to the challenge!
But would you mind showing us
a few moves?
Not that we don't trust you,
but we just want to
admire your skill.
You numbskulls
are not worthy!
Brother Sum.
He doesn't look the part.
These slippers are a little crappy.
Maybe we should
clean him up a bit.
You sure you got the right guy?
Absolutely.
I swear
I did exactly what you told me.
Mr. Beast,
why don't you show us some moves.
Don't be too hard for me!
You dumb or what?
You know what this is, old man?
You ever seen a fist so big?
Don't force me to fight.
I scare myself when I fight!
Then why don't you show me
a few moves?
Hey, is he okay?
Old man, can you fight?
Harder!
You call yourself a mob guy,
hitting like that?
An foreign imported gun!
In all the world of kung fu,
nothing is insurmountable,
but speed is the key.
The Beast is indeed
the best kung fu fighter of all.
The Axe Gang extends its respect!
The best fighters are right here!
Only the World's top killer,
Beast,
has such an aura!
Likewise,
could you two be the Eagle Lovers...
Yang Guo.
And Dragon Fairy.
Indeed a pleasure!
We're here
to deal with the Axe Gang.
And the Axe Gang only.
You should've killed me before.
Coming here today,
you're committing suicide.
We were giving you a few extra days.
You can't escape your fate!
What's this? A funeral bell?
With the Beast here,
let's see whose funeral it will be!
So you're on their side?
Don't get take me wrong.
I only want to kill you,
or be killed by you.
What do you think?
The good and the bad never co-exist.
You cannot escape your destiny.
So be it...
Let's do it
OK, let's do it.
Piece of cake. I can handle this.
Good try, but a little off target.
The Lion's Roar?
Stop!
I didn't know the Lion's Roar
could be done with a speaker!
What a blow!
Looks like he's not up to it!
Indeed. Let's get rid of him
while he's down.
You do it!
I'm gonna puke.
I need to see a doctor.
You go to heck!
You, come over!
- Hit him!
- Yes!
- The head!
- Of course!
- Hit him on the head!
- Okay.
- This is your chance.
- Got it.
- Hit him!
- Hit the darn out of him!
- Right away.
- Hit him!
Beat the darn out of him!
What're you doing?
You want me to hit him
or to hit the darn out of him?
You are making me very confused!
Brother Sum...
Wow, what a big fist!
Why did you hit me?
Where are they?
What's wrong with you?
How could you let them escape?
No one gets away from me!
"Budda Temple"
How did he save us?
He's young.
People always make mistakes.
At least he turned around
at the last moment.
Look at him! Beaten to a pulp!
Tell us your wishes!
Stop it, wait!
Why don't you write in Chinese?
I don't understand!
There's no one!
"Chinese medicine"
It's a miracle
that he lasted this long.
Herbal medicine
should be able to help him.
can only partly help.
The key is his own body structure.
All his bones
and tendons are broken.
It's amazing
that he's recovering so fast.
It is not possible
for normal people.
Unless he is...
What's that smell?
Don't smoke when you're injured.
Let me handle this!
This makes no sense.
Who could've guessed the Beast
would clear the boy's chi flow,
thus unleash
the boy's true potential?
We should've guessed
he is The One!
Is this for real?
You're still alive, you turncoat?
Kill him, men!
What kind of moves are those?
Kids stuff!
If our son were alive,
he would've been his age.
If he studies hard,
he could grow up
to be a doctor or lawyer!
But more likely a stunt man.
Not bad.
I can even stop bullets.
What? The Toad Style
of the Kwan Lun School?
Oh no!
You still remember the Palm.
The move that
falls descends from heaven?
That's the long lost Buddhist Palm.
I surrender...
What kind of move was that?
Want to learn? I'll teach you!
I am truly defeated.
"Sweet Shop"
Hey!
Tell them not to put their snot
on the glass!
You two, put your pants on!
No licking, if you're not buying!
Kid, you have the bone structure
of a kung fu genius.
With that, you can take up
the mission of world peace.
Here is the scroll of
the Buddhist Palm.
I'll let you have it for $10.
Just because it's fate.
Hold on.
There's more to choose from.